还有夫复何求的最好的哥们
and the...best buddy a guy could ever ask for.
这是什么
Oh, what is with this?
-今年没有疯狂面包吗  -对啊
- No crazy bread this year? - Yeah!
我们在纽约又待了五天
We stayed in New York for five more days.
我看到大卫·布莱恩在果冻里
And I saw David Blaine in jello,
我一直超想告诉你  但她们不让
and I've been dying to tell you, but they wouldn't let me!
你真是个废物
You're a disgrace.
天啊  你们妈妈和我
Oh, my God! Your mother and I --
非常愤怒  愤怒
Are furious! Furious!
你们一直待在纽约
You were in New York this whole time,
却什么都没告诉...
and you didn't say anything --
听着  我不知道这一团糟是怎么回事
Now, I don't know what can of worms this is,
但我知道这是我的节日
but I know this is my day,
我要你们都冷静下来
and I want you to calm down.
你口袋里有个手机吗
Is that a phone in your pocket?
这是我的手机
That's my phone.
我从昨天就在找这个手机了
I've been looking for this since yesterday.
我会偷东西了
I steal now.